On that note, we're going to make our sunshine app
100 times better now by connecting it over the network
to the OpenWeatherMap service. OpenWeatherMap provides a free weather data
and forecast API. And the site is linked below, so
you can follow along. By scrolling through the site,
you can see what type of data is available. It
also has example queries so you can click on this
one to see what the weather is like in London.
It includes a user friendly description of the weather
condition, such as broken clouds, in this case. And
we'll use this later in our app. For the
full list of weather conditions, you can go back to
the main page. And scroll down. And then, click
on this link here for the Weather Condition Codes.
And on this page, we have the full list
of weather conditions. It contains everything, from scattered clouds to
freezing rain, or even volcanic ash. I don't know
about you, but hopefully that doesn't happen too often.